

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

#### **Contact**

Tulsa, OK (918) 417-2259 browder.bree@gmail.com

#### Links

**Portfolio** 

GitHub

LinkedIn

### Skills

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

JavaScript

jQuery

React.js

Express.js

Node.js

MongoDB

Python

С

Git

## **Profile**

Front end web developer with a background in user experience. Proven empathetic listener after 1+ years of volunteer work at Reading Partners. Looking to contribute JavaScript focused skill set at a company that values creating equitable technology.

## **Education**

# Google UX Design Professional Certificate, Coursera

JANUARY 2022 - JUNE 2022

- Recipient of the RISE scholarship, awarded by The Mom Project
- Participated in a sixth month certification program that included over 200 hours of instruction
- Completed hundreds of practice-based activities and assessments that simulate real world UX design scenarios

# Diploma of Computer Science and Full Stack Web Development, Holberton School, Tulsa

SEPTEMBER 2020 - JUNE 2022

- Completed a rigorous, fast-paced, software development curriculum focused on project-based, peer learning
- Delivered relevant blog posts to practice verbalizing ideas related to programming

# **Professional Experience**

# Web Design Intern, Reed Design Group, Mansfield

MARCH 2022 - PRESENT

- Identified what could be improved or changed on assigned websites and extrapolated on the information with competitive audits
- Prototyped and wireframed new design ideas for websites

## Software Engineering Student, Holberton School, Tulsa

SEPTEMBER 2020 - JUNE 2022

- Programmed in a hybrid learning environment, both online and on campus
- Engaged in project-based peer learning
- Completed a rigorous curriculum and consistently met project deadlines
- Modeled professional relationships in effort to simulate a real working environment

# **Projects**

# AirBnB Clone v4

JUNE 2021

As part of a team, created a clone of the dynamic web application, Airbnb. It utilized database storage, a back-end API, and a front-end build; using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, Flask, and MySQL.

• Link: https://github.com/lonzor/AirBnB\_clone\_v4

## **Holberton Headphones**

SEPTEMBER 2021

Practiced implementing a designers Figma prototype from scratch in order to create a fully functional product that mirrors the design as closely as possible. The web page was created with HTML and CSS.

• Link: Holberton-Headphones

# **Holberton Smiling School**

OCTOBER 2021

Practiced implementing a designers Figma prototype from scratch in order to create a fully functional product that mirrors the design as closely as possible. The dynamic web application was created with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, and a preconfigured API.

• Link: Holberton-Smiling-School v2